You know the drill!
Slumber Party Massacre is a horror, comedy film directed by Danishka Esterhazy.
Dana, daughter of the only survivor of a massacre in 1993,
is going on a weekend trip with her friends.
After their car breaks down in the very same town where her mother once fought the Driller Killer, Dana and her
friends must come face-to-face with the man who has haunted her mother’s life for the past 30 years.
Dana Devereaux, played by Hannah Gonera.
Maeve, played by Frances Sholto-Douglas.
Alix, played by Mila Rayne.
Breanie, played by Alex McGregor.
Ashley, played by Reze-Tiana Wessels.
Russ Thorne, played by Rob van Vuuren.
Slumber Party Massacre is a 2021 slasher film directed by
Danishka Esterhazy and written by Suzanne Keilly.
It is described as a "modern reimagining" of and stand-alone sequel to the original 1982 film The
Slumber Party Massacre, and the fourth film released in the overall Massacre franchise.
It stars Hannah Gonera, Frances Sholto-Douglas, Alex McGregor, Mila Rayne, Reze-Tiana
Wessels with Schelaine Bennett, Rob van Vuuren and Jennifer Steyn.
It follows a girls' slumber party which becomes a bloodbath when an
escaped mental patient arrives with a power drill.
Studios announced a remake of the film to be helmed by director
Danishka Esterhazy and written by Suzanne Keilly.
Production began in Stellenbosch, South Africa in March
2021, with the cast being announced in April.
Slumber Party Massacre made its world premiere at the Fantastic Fest in Austin, Texas
on September 27, 2021, and was released on Syfy Channel on October 16.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, with praise for its feminist themes, gore and the
performances of the cast, but criticism for its screenplay, character development and pacing.
The film explores themes of slumber party,
sleepover, remake, murder, serial killer.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.